http://bschool.pepperdine.edu/legal/privacy-policy/

Pepperdine University
Pepperdine University ("Pepperdine" or "the university") provides this Web site ("site")
as a service to students, faculty, alumni, and prospective students. Use of the site
is subject to the terms and conditions set forth below in Pepperdine's Privacy Policy
("policy").
Although Pepperdine respects the privacy of this site's users (or "members" or "visitors"),
the university collects information from its Web site members and visitors. The Privacy
Policy governs users' interaction with the site and users' registration for and use
of the site's online services. Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy, the
site's Terms of Service agreement, and/or other published guidelines, Pepperdine does
not release personally identifiable information about the site's visitors without
their permission.
Please note that Pepperdine reviews these privacy practices from time to time, and
that these practices are therefore subject to change. Pepperdine asks users to periodically
review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of
the site's Privacy Policy. To contact Pepperdine about privacy issues, to report a
violation of the site's Privacy Policy, or to raise any other issue regarding the
site, please send an e-mail to webcomm@pepperdine.edu.
The Information Pepperdine Gathers
Pepperdine gathers two types of information about the site's users:
Non-personally identifiable information. As users access the site, Pepperdine collects
and aggregates information indicating, among other things, which pages were visited,
the order in which they were visited, and which hyperlinks were employed. Collecting
such information involves the logging of IP addresses, operating system, and browser
software used by each visitor. Although such information is not personally identifiable,
the university can determine from the IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider
and the geographic location of the user's point of connectivity.
The non-personally identifiable information collected helps in diagnosing any server
problems, administering the site, identifying the most popular areas of the site,
and determining the effectiveness of promotional activities.
For the same purposes, the university uses "cookies" – that is, small text files placed
on your computer's hard drive – to help determine the type of content and sites visited,
the length of time spent on a particular site, and the usage of services offered via
the site. For information on how users can control their Web browser's acceptance
of cookies, please refer to the documentation accompanying the browser.
Pepperdine also uses pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising.
These GIF files are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files
enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn
enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was
placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies
and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and
not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number,
or email address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about
how to opt out of these technologies, go to https://www.google.com/policies/privacy.
Personally identifiable information. Certain areas of the site may require that users
provide personally identifiable information (including, for example, zip code, age,
income, and e-mail address). In addition, when registering to set up an account to
use certain services on the site such as e-mail, chat rooms, forums, or to receive
newsletters or specifically targeted information ("services"), Pepperdine may require
that users provide their name and e-mail address.
The university does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from
children (defined herein as minors younger than thirteen years of age) without obtaining
parental consent. Before registering for an account to use the services of the site,
Pepperdine requests that all minors have their parents read the Privacy Policy and
continue their involvement throughout the registration process.
Pepperdine does not control the acts of this site's members or visitors. All members
and visitors should be aware that their disclosure of personally identifiable information
in a bulletin board, chat room, guest book, or other forum allows other parties to
send them unsolicited e-mail. In the event visitors encounter any user on this site
who is improperly collecting or using information provided by the site's members or
visitors, please contact webcomm@pepperdine.edu.
How the University Uses/Does Not Use Gathered Information
Please take some time to become familiar with the different ways Pepperdine uses the
information gathered. Keep in mind that, while the university encourages all third
parties involved to adhere to this site's Privacy Policy and to otherwise handle personal
information in a responsible manner, Pepperdine cannot and does not assume any responsibility
for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they
use information received either from the university or independently. Nevertheless,
in the event users encounter any third party associated with, or who claims association
with Pepperdine, who is improperly collecting or using personal information, please
contact webcomm@pepperdine.edu who will forward the message to the third party.
Use of non-personally identifiable information. The university uses non-personally
identifiable information in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful online
services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and
behavior of the site visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding
specific areas of the site.
The site may contain links to other Internet Web site, including co-branded or other
affiliated sites that may or may not be owned or operated by Pepperdine. Unless otherwise
explicitly stated, the university is not responsible for the privacy practices or
the content of such sites, including such sites' use of any information (such as IP
number, browser type, or operating system) collected when visitors to the site click
through links to those sites. Even though such information might not identify the
user personally, users should be familiar with the privacy practices of those other
sites.
Use of personally identifiable information. The university provides notice to potential
registrants of this site whose personally identifiable information will be collected
during the registration process. Such notice is provided simultaneously with the user's
registration on this site; moreover, this policy itself serves as notice that such
information is collected under those circumstances. Although users may not "opt out"
of the registration process and still receive access to the services, users may choose
to "opt out" of receiving promotional materials from the university and/or other business
partners. If the user does not "opt out" of receiving such promotional materials,
Pepperdine reserves the right to release user's personally identifiable registration
information to third parties who provide goods or services that the university believes
may be of interest to the user. If the user decides to discontinue receiving promotional
information from such third parties, please contact those third parties directly,
or contact Pepperdine at webcomm@pepperdine.edu.
Pepperdine limits its own e-mail contact and solicitations to those users who have
not "opted out" of receiving such communications. The solicitations are limited in
that they, among other things, will clearly indicate the originator of the e-mail
and provide the user with a method of "opting out" of receiving future communications
of a similar nature.
Finally, Pepperdine may use individual members' data to "pre-populate" forms, which
are displayed for the purpose of collecting individual data by the university. In
no case does pre-populating a form transfer any data to any third party. Only if the
user voluntarily requests that such data be transferred will any transfer take place
– for example, if/when a user clicks a "submit form" button or other button.
Pepperdine reserves the right to release any and all information contained within
access logs concerning any visitor when that visitor is in violation of the university's
"Terms of Service" agreement or other published guidelines, or partakes (or is reasonably
suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant,
or other court order, and to release such information in response to discovery requests,
or in response to any circumstance in which the university, in its sole discretion,
deems an emergency. Pepperdine cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying
those who may be using its servers or services for illegal activities. Pepperdine
also reserves the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement
for investigation or prosecution.
Pepperdine will post the relevant privacy information in the official rules and/or
registration area for any promotions it sponsors. That privacy information, to the
extent it conflicts with this Privacy Policy, will govern that particular promotion.
Security
All information gathered on the site is stored within a controlled database accessible
only to the university to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information
under its control. However, as effective as any security measure implemented by the
university may be, no security system is impenetrable. Pepperdine cannot guarantee
the security of its database, nor can it guarantee that the information supplied by
users will not be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet. Questions
regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to webcomm@pepperdine.edu.
Your Rights
Where authorized and subject to all applicable laws, you may have the right to request
access to, a copy of, rectification, restriction in the use of, or erasure of your
information. You also have the right to withdraw consent to the use of your information,
without affecting the legitimacy of the University's use of the information prior
to receipt of your request.
If users would like to have personally identifiable information changed or removed
from Pepperdine’s database, please contact webcomm@pepperdine.edu. Keep in mind that there will be residual information remaining within the databases,
access logs, and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable
information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however,
the university reserves the right, from time to time, to re-contact former customers
or users of this site if lawful.
Information collected in the European Union will be transferred out of the European
Union to the University. If you believe that the University has not complied with
applicable foreign laws regulating such data or data transfers, you have the right
to file a complaint with the appropriate authorities.
Updates to this Policy
We may update or change this policy at any time. Your continued use of this site after
any such change indicates your acceptance of such changes.
Questions?
Questions regarding the Privacy Policy should be directed to the university at webcomm@pepperdine.edu.
Pepperdine University24255 Pacific Coast HighwayMalibu, CA 90263
scroll up
©
